{
	"questions": [
		{
			"id": "question1",
			"prompt": "Столица Франции",
			"choices": [
				{ "id": "a", "content": "Берн" },
				{ "id": "b", "content": "Вена" },
				{ "id": "c", "content": "Мадрид" },
				{ "id": "d", "content": "Париж" }
			],
			"answer": "d"
		},
		{
			"id": "question2",
			"prompt": "Столица Италии",
			"choices": [
				{ "id": "a", "content": "Рим" },
				{ "id": "b", "content": "Рига" },
				{ "id": "c", "content": "Монако" },
				{ "id": "d", "content": "Дублин" }
			],
			"answer": "a"
		},
		{
			"id": "question3",
			"prompt": "Столица Великобритании",
			"choices": [
				{ "id": "a", "content": "Осло" },
				{ "id": "b", "content": "Лондон" },
				{ "id": "c", "content": "Лиссабон" },
				{ "id": "d", "content": "Таллин" }
			],
			"answer": "b"
		},
		{
			"id": "question4",
			"prompt": "Столица Эстонии",
			"choices": [
				{ "id": "a", "content": "Тирана" },
				{ "id": "b", "content": "Рига" },
				{ "id": "c", "content": "Таллин" },
				{ "id": "d", "content": "Стокгольм" }
			],
			"answer": "c"
		},
		{
			"id": "question5",
			"prompt": "Столица России",
			"choices": [
				{ "id": "a", "content": "Киев" },
				{ "id": "b", "content": "Минск" },
				{ "id": "c", "content": "Москва" },
				{ "id": "d", "content": "Кишинёв" }
			],
			"answer": "c"
		},
		{
			"id": "question6",
			"prompt": "Столица Германии",
			"choices": [
				{ "id": "a", "content": "Прага" },
				{ "id": "b", "content": "Рига" },
				{ "id": "c", "content": "Вена" },
				{ "id": "d", "content": "Берлин" }
			],
			"answer": "d"
		},
		{
			"id": "question7",
			"prompt": "Столица Нидерландов",
			"choices": [
				{ "id": "a", "content": "Афины" },
				{ "id": "b", "content": "Братислава" },
				{ "id": "c", "content": "Амстердам" },
				{ "id": "d", "content": "Осло" }
			],
			"answer": "c"
		},
		{
			"id": "question8",
			"prompt": "Столица Хорватии",
			"choices": [
				{ "id": "a", "content": "Загреб" },
				{ "id": "b", "content": "Сан-Марино" },
				{ "id": "c", "content": "Белград" },
				{ "id": "d", "content": "Загреб" }
			],
			"answer": "d"
		},
		{
			"id": "question9",
			"prompt": "Столица Ирана",
			"choices": [
				{ "id": "a", "content": "Тегеран" },
				{ "id": "b", "content": "Исламабад" },
				{ "id": "c", "content": "Астана" },
				{ "id": "d", "content": "Ташкент" }
			],
			"answer": "a"
		},
		{
			"id": "question10",
			"prompt": "Столица Туркменистана",
			"choices": [
				{ "id": "a", "content": "Ташкент" },
				{ "id": "b", "content": "Ашхабад" },
				{ "id": "c", "content": "Астана" },
				{ "id": "d", "content": "Хазар" }
			],
			"answer": "a"
		}
	]
}
